Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ajmal-abid-7929b7200 (LinkedIn)

+91 90616 23937

ajmalammal9745@gmail.com

Top Skills

Marketing

Sales

Customer Service

Management & Planning

Collaborative Problem Soloving

Forcasting

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Malayalam (Native or Bilingual)

Hindi (Elementary)

Tamil (Elementary)

Ajmal Abid

Marketing Executive at Goldmedal Electricals Pvt. Ltd. Kannur

Summary

A systematic, organized, hardworking and dedicated team player with an analytical bend of mind with good academic credentials. I have experience of years across as Sales, Administration. And as a focused determined and confident individual, I can be relied upon to deliver challenging targets whilst ensuring the team.

Experience

Goldmedal Electricals Pvt. Ltd.

Marketing Executive

June 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Kannur, Kerala, India

Responsibility and Achievements

- •Increased sales over 50%, working directly with clients to develop report, build sales based on needs and desires, and close deals promptly.
- •Provided outstanding and professional customer support resulting in 100% customer satisfaction rating.
- •Handled account details regularly through email and phone in a timely manner.
- •Managed office responsibilities such as daily inventory of products, staff scheduling, office organization, and promotional events.
- •Engaging and tactics approach on problems for solving in minimum time period

Dhoti club
Sales man
October 2018 - December 2018 (3 months)
Thalassery, Kerala, India

Attented and Provided consultation and recommendation to customers regarding types of supplements and assist to meet there wants and desires satisfactfully

Goldmedal Electricals Pvt. Ltd. field promotion January 2018 - January 2018 (1 month) Kannur, Kerala, India

gold medal system and automations new app introduction and promotion work called dhanbarse done.

Education

Jain (Deemed-to-be University)

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Marketing · (2021 - 2023)

Kannur University, Kannur Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Marketing · (2017 - 2020)